immigrationboards.com 2019-12-13

# Privacy Notice | Workpermit.com

## Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:

Our Commitment To Privacy   
The Information We Collect   
How We Use Information   
Our Commitment To Data Security   
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information  
GDPR and Users from European Union  
How To Contact Us

### Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us at workpermit.com. Please note that immigrationboards.com is a workpermit.com site.  To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

### 

### The Information We Collect:

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on this website. On some pages, you can ask for an immigration assessment, go ahead with a visa application, order products, make requests, subscribe to our message board or newsletter and register to receive materials. You can unsubscribe at any time to the workpermit.com Newsletter or immigrationboards.com The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

 **To subscribe to our newsletter or immigrationboards.com we will typically require some or all of the following information.**

  * Name 
  * Address 
  * Email address 
  * Phone number

 **For an immigration assessment we will typically require the following information:**

  * Current Immigration Status
  * Work Experience
  * Age
  * Nationality
  * Skills and Qualifications
  * Current State of Health
  * If relevant details of employer and job offer
  * If relevant details of family

 **The Information We DONT Collect:**

Credit/Debit Card Information

### The Way We Use Information:

We use the information you provide about yourself or someone else to provide regular email updates, immigration advice, to help with a visa or work permit application, to deal with particular enquiries or to send you an item ordered from our site. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary as required under the law and except where this information is needed for a work permit or visa application as instructed by you.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. We will not use your e-mail address for any other purpose, or share your e-mail address with outside parties, unless you have given us your specific consent to do so.

You can register with our website if you would like to receive our newsletter, subscribe to immigrationboards.com, receive catalog or updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you have given us your specific consent to do so.

Our most common method of shipping is FedEx, UPS or TNT. If you provide us with your e-mail address we will enter it onto the relevant web-site for online status tracking. This will allow us to confirm by e-mail your scheduled delivery and tracking number. workpermit.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other web sites.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

### Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

For example when you place an order online, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us.

### 

### How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by calling us on +44 (0)344 9919222 or sending us an email. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request with details of the error.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

### GDPR and Users from European Union

Your data will be kept for as long as reasonably necessary taking into account local regulations and the use of the data.  Your details relating to subscription services such as the workpermit.com Newsletter and immigrationboards.com will be kept for at least as long as the period that you are a subscriber to these services.

 _You are entitled to view, amend, or delete the personal information that we hold.Email your request to our data protection officer._

### How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us .
